<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Economikit Alliance</title>
    <link>https://economikit.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Economikit Alliance</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://economikit.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Engagement Criteria</title>
      <link>https://economikit.org/how-we-work/engagement-criteria/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://economikit.org/how-we-work/engagement-criteria/</guid>
      <description>What anchors or waypoints help us make coherent decisions about who to align with or what to work on?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Context - Why?</title>
      <link>https://economikit.org/blog/2021/05/the-context-why/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://economikit.org/blog/2021/05/the-context-why/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The following attempts to distill the shared context we have developed over the last year and a half. The guiding question motivating this work is, &amp;ldquo;what is it about the confluence of digital technology and global economic circuits that needs to change?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://economikit.org/homepage/01-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://economikit.org/homepage/01-intro/</guid>
      <description>We are an allied group of intersectional strategists, ethicists, cultural anthropologists and software creators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://economikit.org/homepage/02-how-we-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://economikit.org/homepage/02-how-we-work/</guid>
      <description>How we work Presenting a vision of stewardship for the Holochain ecosystem and its intersection with other projects promoting justice and autonomy from systems of economic oppression.
Read our engagement criteria.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://economikit.org/homepage/03-what-we-are-creating/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://economikit.org/homepage/03-what-we-are-creating/</guid>
      <description>What we are creating We build and consult on the use of software tools which provision for the necessities of life whilst making possible complex cross-cultural intersections and humane and vibrant modes of relating, exchanging, and caring for self, other, and community.
Tools for economic autonomy ValueFlows Meeting the challenges of our times requires not just a new economic system, but a new measurement system. The ValueFlows protocol reimagines accounting as a rich multidimensional weave of attributable information that can be deeply representative of reality, and enables P2P coordination of all kinds of resource flows in networks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
